A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Environmental Quality International (Eqi) Ltd. (10251217), 2002 May 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 8963)
    Middle East; Africa, North; Environmental Quality International (Eqi) Ltd.
  - Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia (09501208), 1995 July 01-1997 September 30 (Reel 8233)
    ANALYSIS AND ADVOCACY OF POLICIES PROMOTING RIGHTS OF TRADITIONAL POPULATIONS TO NATURAL RESOURCES IN THE AMAZON REGION OF BRAZIL
    Brazil; Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia
  - Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia (09701248), 1997 July 01-1999 June 30 (Reel 8664)
    RESEARCH, ADVOCACY, AND TRAINING ON SUSTAINABLE LAND USE PRACTICES AND INDIGENOUS RESOURCE RIGHTS IN THE AMAZON
  - Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia (09901466), 1999 July 01-2001 August 31 (Reel 9104)
    APPLIED RESEARCH, ADVOCACY, AND TRAINING TO PROMOTE THE ECONOMIC AND ECOLOGICAL VIABILITY OF SMALLHOLDER PRODUCTION AND AGRARIAN REFORM SETTLEMENTS IN THE EASTERN AMAZON
    Brazil; Land reform--Brazil; Ecology -- Research -- Brazil; Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia
  - Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia (10001274), 2000 June 01-2002 September 30 (Reel 9116)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH, ADVOCACY, PUBLIC FORA, AND EDUCATION ON ENVIRONMENTAL SERVICES, FOREST CONSERVATION, AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT IN BRAZIL
    Brazil; Conservation of natural resources -- Brazil; Sustainable development--Brazil; Forest management -- Brazil; Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia
  - Environmental Research Institute of Amazonia (10251261), 2002 July 01-2003 September 30 (Reel 9279)
    Core support for research, advocacy, public forums and education on forest conservation, sustainable development and climate change in the Amazon
  - Environmental Safety (08550855), 1985 July 25-1986 July 24 (Reel 4320;5379;7747)
    SUPPORT FOR PARTICIPANTS' COSTS IN A WORKSHOP ON LEGAL SAFEGUARDS AGAINST TOXIC, CHEMICAL AND OTHER ENVIRONMENTAL DAMAGE
    Sudarshan, R.
    India; Environmental Safety
  - Environmental Support Center (10101980), 2001 August 01-2002 July 31 (Reel 9021)
    Core support to expand its activities to increase the capacity of community-based environmental justice organizations
    United States; Environmental justice -- United States; Environmental policy -- United States -- Citizen participation; Environmental Support Center
  - Environmental Working Group (10351914), 2003 September 01-2004 August 31 (Reel 9077)
    For a public education strategy to encourage the growth of policies favoring equitable and sustainable rural development across the United States
    United States; Environmental Working Group
  - Enyi-Kokome Rural Development Union (09250287), 1991 November 01-1995 November 30 (Reel 7236;7351;8657)
    SUPPORT FOR MANAGEMENT TRAINING AND CREDIT FOR A RURAL WOMEN'S ASSOCIATION (NIGERIA)
    $29,000.00;$29,000.00
    Nigeria; Enyi-Kokome Rural Development Union
  - Enyi-Kokome Rural Development Union (09401226), 1994 September 01-2000 December 31 (Reel 8571)
    SUPPORT FOR INSTITUTION-BUILDING AND CREDIT FOR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATIONS IN NIGERIA
  - Epidavros Project (09701091), 1997 May 01-2000 February 29 (Reel 8353)
    SUPPORT FOR PROMOTIONAL AND OUTREACH ACTIVITIES IN CONNECTION WITH A DOCUMENTARY FILM ON THE POLITICAL ASYLUM PROCESS IN THE UNITED STATES
    $380,000.00;$380,000.00
    Higashi, Taryn
    United States; Epidavros Project
  - Epidavros Project (10150518), 2001 January 01-2001 October 31 (Reel 8828)
    Planning grant to study the feasibility of a documentary film on the unfolding campaign for legalization of undocumented immigrants
    Higashi, Taryn;Santos, John Phillip
    United States; Mass media; Human rights advocacy -- United States; Refugees--Legal status, laws, etc.; Epidavros Project
  - Episcopal Church of the Sudan (08500647), 1985 July 01-1995 October 31 (Reel 7086)
    SUPPORT FOR LAINYA VOCATIONAL TRAINING SCHOOL IN SOUTHERN SUDAN
    $690,000.00;$690,000.00
    Longhurst, Richard;Davies, Humphrey T.
    Sudan; Episcopal Church of the Sudan
  - Episcopal Church of the Sudan (08650834), 1986 August 01-1988 July 31 (Reel 5785;5975)
    SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT PLANNING/COORDINATOR OFFICER IN THE SOUTHERN SUDAN
    Longhurst, Richard
  - Episcopal Commission of Social Action (09100901), 1991 May 01-1993 July 31 (Reel 7858)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING AND NETWORKING OF HUMAN RIGHTS MONITORS IN PERU
    $102,000.00;$102,000.00
    Tillett, Anthony D.
    Peru; Episcopal Commission of Social Action
  - Episcopal Conference of Haiti (08850645), 1988 June 10-1990 October 31 (Reel 6125)
    SUPPORT FOR RADIO SOLEIL'S PROGRAMS
    Heisler, Michele;Sanborn, Cynthia
    Haiti; Episcopal Conference of Haiti
  - Equal Access International (10350766), 2003 April 01-2006 March 31 (Reel 9204)
    To address issues of HIV/AIDS and women's rights in Nepal using radio and other appropriate information and communication technology
    Goswami, Roshmi, Dr.
    Nepal; Equal Access International
  - Equal Justice Works (08750490), 1987 April 01-1989 June 30 (Reel 5809)
    SUPPORT OF ITS INCOME SHARING PROGRAM ENABLING LAW STUDENTS AND GRADUATES TO WORK AS INTERNS
    McClymont, Mary (Mary E.)
    United States; Equal Justice Works
  - Equal Justice Works (08900505), 1989 July 01-1997 March 31 (Reel 7341)
    SUPPORT FOR TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE AND TRAINING ACTIVITIES TO SUPPORT LAW STUDENT PROGRAMS BENEFITTING THE POOR
    Neuborne, Helen
    United States; Public interest law--United States; Equal Justice Works
  - Equal Justice Works (09100819), 1991 July 01-1997 March 31 (Reel 7425)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PUBLIC INTEREST LAW FELLOWSHIP PROJECT
    United States; Public interest law; Equal Justice Works
  - Equal Justice Works (09450318), 1994 January 01-1994 June 30 (Reel 6677)
    PROJECT SUPPORT FOR TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE AND RESOURCE DEVELOPMENT EFFORT RELATED TO NATIONAL SERVICE PROGRAM
  - Equal Justice Works (09950424), 1999 January 01-2000 December 31 (Reel 9046)
    SUPPORT FOR BOARD DEVELOPMENT AND IMPROVING MANAGEMENT, FINANCIAL, AND COMPUTER SYSTEMS
    Romero, Anthony D.
  - Equal Justice Works (10001286), 2000 July 01-2003 June 30 (Reel 9024)
    SUPPORT FOR THE NATIONAL SERVICE LEGAL CORPS AND TO PLAN A NATIONAL LEADRSHIP DEVELOPMENT CENTER FOR POSTGRADUATE LEGAL FELLOWS PURSUING PUBLIC INTEREST LAW.
    PSJ - Office of the Vice President
    United States; Law --Study and teaching--United States; Law --Scholarships, fellowships, etc.--United States; Public interest law--Study and teaching--United States; Equal Justice Works
  - Equal Justice Works (10101826), 2001 July 01-2003 June 30 (Reel 9079)
    Core support for the National Service Legal Corps and to develop an overall communications strategy for the association
    $410,000.00;$410,000.00
  - Equal Rights Advocates (07950612), 1979 June 01-1980 May 31 (Reel 2708)
    SUPPORT FOR A FEASIBILITY STUDY FOR A NATIONAL WOMENS LAW FOUNDATION
    $2,900.00;$2,900.00
    Equal Rights Advocates
  - Equal Rights Advocates (08550615), 1985 June 13-1987 June 12 (Reel 5300)
    SUPPORT FOR THE CREATION AND DISSEMINATION OF AN ANNOTATED BIBLIOGRAPHY ON PAY EQUITY
    Forman, Shepard;Zeitlin, June H.
    United States; Equal Rights Advocates
  - Equal Rights Advocates (08550729), 1985 June 01-1986 May 30 (Reel 4821)
    SUPPORT TO FACILITATE THE IMPLEMENTATION OF LONG-TERM DIVERSIFIED FUNDRAISING STRATEGIES
  - Equal Rights Advocates (08600631), 1986 May 01-1998 March 31 (Reel 7623;8449)
    FOR SUPPORT OF LITIGATION, ADVOCACY, POLICY RESEARCH AND RELATED ACTIVITIES ASSOCIATED WITH THE ADVANCEMENT OF WOMEN
    $1,950,000.00;$1,950,000.00
    Zeitlin, June H.;Neuborne, Helen
  - Equal Rights Advocates (09500913), 1995 April 01-1996 September 30 (Reel 7085)
    LITIGATION, ADVOCACY AND PUBLIC EDUCATION ON AFFIRMATIVE ACTION
  - Equal Rights Advocates (09701331), 1997 May 01-1999 April 30 (Reel 8048)
    CAPACITY-BUILDING INITIATIVE
    Phillips, Barbara
  - Equal Rights Advocates (09800936), 1998 April 01-2000 March 31 (Reel 8335)
    SUPPORT FOR LITIGATION, ADVOCACY, POLICY RESEARCH AND RELATED ACTIVITIES ASSOCIATED WITH THE ADVANCEMENT OF WOMEN
    United States; Women's rights--United States; Equal Rights Advocates
  - Equal Rights Advocates (10101777), 2001 June 01-2004 May 31 (Reel 9115)
    For the Higher Education Research and Advocacy Project and for relocation costs
    $800,000.00;$800,000.00
    United States; Women's rights--United States; Human rights -- United States; Equal Rights Advocates
  - Equal Rights Advocates (10201130), 2007 May 01-2008 October 31 (Reel 9080)
    Core support for the Tradeswomen Legal Advocacy Project to engage the public, policy makers and the courts in supporting affirmative action for women in construction trades
    Phillips, Barbara;Rios, Sara;Silliman, Jael Miriam
    Date Restricted Material -- Contains grant records inactive for less than 10 years -- Restricted records are Open to scholarly research in 2019.
  - Equal Rights Center (10051939), 2000 July 01-2002 June 30 (Reel 8875)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND ADVOCACY ON RACIAL DISCRIMINATION IN HOUSING, EMPLOYMENT, AND PUBLIC SERVICES
    Rios, Sara
    United States; Discrimination in Employment -- Research -- United States; Discrimination in Housing -- Research -- United States; Civil rights -- United States -- Research; Equal Rights Center
  - Equal Rights Center (10251208), 2002 July 01-2004 June 30 (Reel 9076)
    For research and advocacy on racial discrimination in housing, employment and public accommodations
    United States; Equal Rights Center
  - Equality NOW (09751473), 1997 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel 8130)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO STRENGTHEN AN INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S ACTION NETWORK AIMED AT PROTECTING THE HUMAN RIGHTS OF WOMEN AROUND THE WORLD
    Global; Equality NOW
  - Equality NOW (09951092), 1999 May 01-2000 April 30 (Reel 8498)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CAMPAIGN ON MONITORING THE IMPLEMENTATION OF THE COMMITMENTS MADE BY GOVERNMENTS AT THE BEIJING WOMEN'S CONF.
    Cox, Larry;Romero, Anthony D.
    Global; Women's rights--Global; Equality NOW
  - Equality NOW (10001700), 2000 July 01-2001 June 30 (Reel 8638)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO PROMOTE AND COORDINATE A GLOBAL MEDIA AND ADVOCACY EVENT IN FEBRUARY 2001 FOCUSED ON VIOLENCE AGAINST WOMEN
    Global; Victims of Family violence--Global; Women--Crimes against--Global; Human rights advocacy -- Global; Equality NOW
  - Equality NOW (10101596), 2001 May 01-2003 April 30 (Reel 9029)
    General support for the communcations activities of its worldwide, rapid response grassroots action network of women's rights organizations and individual activists
    Global; Women's rights--Global; Human rights -- Global; Equality NOW
  - Equality NOW (10250246), 2001 November 01-2002 January 31 (Reel 8889)
    To organize a conference and meetings for Afghan women's groups to promote their rights in the peace and reconstruction of Afghanistan
    Ispahani, Mahnaz Z.
    Afghanistan; Equality NOW
  - Equator Foundation Incorporated (08750212), 1987 January 07-1988 May 07 (Reel 4861;5537)
    SUPPORT FOR THE START-UP PHASE OF A SMALL ENTERPRISE ASSISTANCE PROGRAM IN TANZANIA
    $19,600.00;$13,894.45
    Tanzania; Equator Foundation Incorporated
  - Equity Trust, Inc. (09151114), 1991 July 15-1992 July 15 (Reel 6352;6705)
    STRATEGIC ANALYSIS ON THE POTENTIAL OF THE COMMUNITY LAND TRUST MODEL TO DELIVER AFFORDABLE HOUSING TO THE URBAN POOR IN KENYA
    $24,000.00;$21,950.25
    Miller, Thomas F.
    Kenya; Equity Trust, Inc.
  - Eran - Israeli Association for Emotional First Aid by Phone (10251380), 2002 July 01-2003 June 30 (Reel 9022)
    To expand and strengthen a telephone hotline service providing emergency mental health counseling to the Israeli public
    Israel; Eran - Israeli Association for Emotional First Aid by Phone
  - Erase Racism (10550282), 2004 November 01-2005 October 31 (Reel 9242)
    General support to identify and address policies that perpetuate institutional racism in the systems that affect the daily life of Long Island residents
    New York (State); Erase Racism
  - Erikson Institute (09350602), 1993 April 01-1994 March 31 (Reel 6618)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING SEMINARS FOR SCHOOL STAFF ON DEVELOPMENTAL ISSUES RESULTING FROM CHRONIC TRAUMATIC VIOLENCE
    Molnar, Janice M.
    Chicago (Ill.); Erikson Institute
  - Erikson Institute (09551135), 1995 July 01-1996 November 30 (Reel 7343)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON THE HISTORY OF PROVIDING NEIGHBORHOOD-BASED SOCIAL SERVICES FOR POOR FAMILIES
    $38,200.00;$38,200.00
    United States; Community-based family services -- United States; Poor families; Social services; Social settlements; Erikson Institute
  - Erskine College (05600866), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0330)
    TO RAISE TEACHERS' SALARIES IN PRIVATE LIBERAL ARTS AND SCIENCE COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES IN USA & TERR. (ENDOW. GENERAL SUPPORT)
    $108,500.00;$108,500.00
    Erskine College
  - Escuela Agricola Pan-Americana, Inc. (06900061), 1968 November 08-1971 November 07 (Reel 1588;3200)
    SUPPORT FOR GUARANTEE FUND FOR STUDENT LOANS
    $200,000.00;$.00
    Escuela Agricola Pan-Americana, Inc.
  - Escuela Agricola Pan-Americana, Inc. (09650284), 1996 January 01-1997 January 31 (Reel 7783)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND A WORKSHOP ON INTERMEDIATE MARKETING FOR SMALL-SCALE PRODUCERS IN CENTRAL AMERICA
    $59,000.00;$57,562.70
    Conroy, Michael E.;Salgado, Patricia Krackov
    Central America; Escuela Agricola Pan-Americana, Inc.
  - Eskor Toyo Centre (10050457), 2000 April 01-2004 January 31 (Reel 9119)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH AND EMPOWERMENT PROJECT TO INCREASE POLITICAL CONSCIOUSNESS, ORGANIZATION, AND ACTION AMONG MICROMINORITIES IN NIGERIA
    West Africa (Lagos);Governance and Civil Society
    Nigeria; Multiculturalism--Nigeria; Civil society -- Nigeria; Eskor Toyo Centre
  - Eskwelahan sang Katawhan Negros, Inc. (10250918), 2002 April 01-2003 March 31 (Reel 9063)
    For a pilot project to build the capacity of school boards, school officials, teachers and parents associations to collaborate to improve the reading competencies of children
    Philippines; Eskwelahan sang Katawhan Negros, Inc.
  - Esperanca Foundation (08850213), 1988 January 01-1988 December 31 (Reel 5538;5771)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON HEALTH OF BREASTFEEDING MOTHERS AND THEIR CHILDREN IN THE CENTRAL AMAZON
    $34,514.00;$34,514.00
    Brazil; Esperanca Foundation
  - Esperanza Community Housing Corporation (10200985), 2002 May 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9010)
    To conduct a first-year assessment of the Mercado La Paloma public market in South Central Los Angeles
    Los Angeles (Calif.); Income -- United States; Community development -- Economic aspects -- United States; Economic Security (Law) -- United States; Poor--United States; Esperanza Community Housing Corporation
  - Espiral Consultants (09551070), 1995 July 01-1998 May 31 (Reel 7772)
    SUPPORT FOR DEVELOPING AND DISSEMINATING A TRAINING PROGRAM TO ENHANCE NGOS' INSTITUTIONAL DEVELOPMENT
    Mexico; Espiral Consultants
  - Espiral Consultants (09801297), 1998 June 01-2001 March 31 (Reel 8760)
    FOLLOW-ON SUPPORT FOR DEVELOPING AND DISSEMINATING A TRAINING PROGRAM TO ENHANCE NGO INSTITUTIONAL DEVELOPMENT
    Farias Campero, Pablo;Faulhaber, Ingrid S.
    Mexico; Humanitarianism--Information services--Mexico; Civil society -- Mexico; Espiral Consultants
  - Espiral Consultants (10050854), 2000 March 01-2000 December 31 (Reel 8659)
    SUPPORT FOR PROCESS OF NATIONAL CONSULTATION AMONG MEXICAN NONGOVERNMENTAL ORGANIZATIONS IN PREPARATION FOR THE SUMMIT OF THE AMERICAS TO BE HELD IN QUEBEC IN APRIL 2001
    Mexico; Non-governmental organizations--Mexico; Civil society -- Congresses; Espiral Consultants
  - Espiral Consultants (10101697), 2001 June 01-2004 February 29 (Reel 9044)
    For a co-investment fund to support participation of civil society organizations in social development projects in Chiapas, Mexico
    $438,000.00;$438,000.00
    Brown, Kimberli R.;Farias Campero, Pablo
    Mexico; Sustainable development--Mexico--Chiapas (Mexico)--Citizen participation; Civil society -- Mexico -- Chiapas -- Citizen participation; Espiral Consultants
  - Espiral Consultants (10150974), 2001 April 01-2002 March 31 (Reel 9043)
    Create a clearinghouse for information on processes of civil society strengthening at the federal and state levels in Mexico
    Mexico; Civics -- Study and teaching -- Mexico; Civil society -- Mexico -- Information services; Espiral Consultants
  - Esquel Group Foundation Incorporated (08950305), 1989 March 30-1990 March 30 (Reel 5832)
    TO STRENGTHEN A NETWORK OF LATIN AMERICAN INSTITUTIONS DEVELOPING REGIONAL RESEARCH-ACTION PROGRAMS IN THE INFORMAL SECTOR
    Latin America; Esquel Group Foundation Incorporated
  - Essex County, New Jersey (09401325), 1994 October 01-1998 June 30 (Reel 7905)
    SUPPORT TO ENHANCE THE EFFECTIVENESS AND BROADEN THE IMPACT OF PROJECT CARE
    $20,000.00;$18,775.54
    United States; Essex County, New Jersey
  - Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility (09900264), 1998 November 01-1999 October 31 (Reel 8440)
    START-UP SUPPORT FOR AN ORGANIZATION TO PROMOTE CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY IN BRAZIL
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Governance and Civil Society
    Leeds, Elizabeth R.;Lindblom, Lance E.
    Brazil; Social responsibility of business--Brazil; Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility
  - Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility (10001996), 2000 September 01-2002 August 31 (Reel 8937)
    START-UP SUPPORT FOR AN ORGANIZATION TO PROMOTE CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY IN THE AMERICAS
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);Mexico and Central America (Mexico City);Andean Region and Southern Cone (Santiago)
    Brooke, Nigel P.;Farias Campero, Pablo;Varas, Augusto
    Canada; Latin America; United States; Social responsibility of business--Brazil; Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility
  - Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility (10050602), 2000 February 01-2001 June 30 (Reel 8655)
    SUPPORT FOR A PROGRAM TO PROVIDE MEDIA TRAINING AND EXPAND COVERAGE OF ISSUES OF CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY
    $100,000.00;$99,454.70
    Leeds, Elizabeth R.
    Brazil; Social responsibility of business--Brazil; Mass media--Moral and ethical aspects--Brazil; Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility
  - Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility (10250173), 2001 October 01-2002 September 30 (Reel 9021)
    For media training and capacity building to promote a culture of corporate social responsibility
    Brazil; Ethos Institute of Business and Social Responsibility
  - Etnollano Foundation (08850332), 1988 January 01-1991 June 30 (Reel 6332)
    SUPPORT FOR COMPARATIVE RESEARCH ON PUBLIC AND PRIVATE CHILD SURVIVAL PROGRAMS AMONG ISOLATED INDIAN & BLACK COMMUNITIES IN COLOMBIA
    $73,400.00;$73,400.00
    Colombia; Etnollano Foundation
  - Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation (09600793), 1996 June 01-1998 December 31 (Reel 7873)
    SUPPORT TO ESTABLISH A FUND FOR PROJECTS THAT IMPROVE INTERGROUP RELATIONS IN THE WASHINGTON, D.C. METROPOLITAN AREA
    Washington; Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation
  - Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation (09851239), 1998 July 01-2000 March 31 (Reel 9042)
    SUPPORT FOR THE INITIATIVE TO STRENGTHEN NEIGHBORHOOD INTER-GROUP ASSETS
    Washington; Intergroup relations -- United States; Race relations--United States; Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation
  - Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation (09900331), 1999 January 01-2000 December 31 (Reel 8593)
    TO IMPLEMENT REGRANTING PROGRAMS AIMED AT MOBILIZING INTERGROUP STRATEGIES FOR ADVANCEMENT TOWARDS SHARED GOALS
    Atlanta (Ga.); Miami (Fla.); Minneapolis (Minn.); Immigrants -- Services for -- Washington (D.C); Community development -- Washington (D.C.) -- Citizen participation; Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc. (06800726), 1968 July 01-1969 August 31 (Reel 2447)
    SUPPORT OF A SUMMER INSTITUTE FOR YOUNG CRITICS IN THE ARTS
    $18,458.00;$18,458.00
    D'Arms, Edward F.
    Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc.
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc. (07000124), 1970 January 01-1970 December 31 (Reel 1670)
    EXPERIMENTAL WORKSHOP IN THEATRICAL COMMUNICATION TO BE CONDUCTED BY THE NATIONAL THEATRE OF THE DEAF
    $15,290.00;$15,290.00
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc. (07300175), 1973 February 01-1975 March 31 (Reel 1506;3035)
    DEMONSTRATION IN THEATER TRAINING AND STYLE DRAWING UPON BRITISH AND AMERICAN TRADITIONS
    Kapp, Richard P.
    Great Britain; New York (State); Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc.
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc. (08100552), 1980 July 01-1985 June 30 (Reel 4649)
    TO IMPROVE AND STABILIZE THE FINANCIAL POSITION
    $292,489.00;$292,489.00
    Connecticut; Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc.
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center, Inc. (08151054), 1982 January 01-1984 June 30 (Reel 4672)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE PREPARATION OF THE GRAPHICS FOR A VOLUME BY GEORGE IZENOUR ENTITLED "THEATER TECHNOLOGY"
  - Eugenio Mendoza Foundation (07750085), 1976 September 01-1978 November 10 (Reel 3086;3805)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH PROJECT ON PRESCHOOL EDUCATION
    Venezuela; Eugenio Mendoza Foundation
  - Eureka Communities (09701562), 1997 August 01-2001 January 31 (Reel 8677)
    SUPPORT FOR LEADERSHIP TRAINING, NETWORKING, AND SABBATICALS FOR NGO LEADERS
    $1,500,000.00;$1,500,000.00
    Vaid, Urvashi
    United States; Eureka Communities
  - Eureka Communities (10100659), 2001 February 01-2003 December 31 (Reel 9193)
    Support for a fellowship program for leaders of community service organizations and for institutional capacity-building in the areas of development and communications
    Governance and Civil Society;Community and Resource Development;Unit Reserve
    Edwards, Michael;Duncan, Cynthia M.;Gaberman, Barry D.
    United States; Community development -- United States; Civil society -- United States -- Citizen participation; Eureka Communities
  - Eureka Communities (10550128), 2004 September 01-2005 December 31 (Reel 9080)
    For peer-to-peer learning fellowships for senior executives from the Public Education Network
    $141,600.00;$141,600.00
  - Eureka Communities (10550882), 2005 July 01-2005 December 31 (Reel 9243)
    General support to increase the capacity of leaders of community-based organizations working to improve the lives of poor people
    Unit Reserve
  - Euro-Mediterranean Human Rights Network (10150215), 2000 October 01-2001 September 30 (Reel 8959)
    Support for a conference in October 2000 on the future of Palestinian refugees under the current peace process
    $80,000.00;$79,262.20
    Azzam, Fatih Samih
    Middle East; Refugees--Palestine--Congresses; Euro-Mediterranean Human Rights Network
  - Euro-Mediterranean Human Rights Network (10250347), 2001 September 01-2005 February 28 (Reel 9235)
    For a program of legal counseling and advocacy for refugees and asylum seekers in Lebanon
    Azzam, Fatih Samih;Playfair, Emma
    Lebanon; Human rights advocacy -- Lebanon; Refugees--Lebanon; Palestinian Arabs--Lebanon; Euro-Mediterranean Human Rights Network
  - European Association of Management Training Centers (06000043), 1959 December 18-1962 December 17 (Reel 0563)
    European Association of Management Training Centers
  - European Association of Management Training Centers (07000204), 1970 October 23-1973 October 22 (Reel 1659)
    START UP AND PROGRAM COSTS OF THE EUROPEAN FUND FOR MANAGEMENT DEVELOPMENT AND EDUCATION
    $150,000.00;$64,000.00